Hey, look Amazing Spider-Man 193.
(Sheldon:)Got it.
(Howard:)Remember this one?
Spider-Man loses a big fight...
(Howard:)...and then his girlfriend breaks up
with him.
You want me to get it for you?
It will help take your mind off things.
(Stuart:)Hey, guys. What's going on?
Ah, we need to kill a couple hours
until the next showing.
(Stuart:)Oh, well, no problem.
(Stuart:)I was thinking of closing early,
and going home...
...but let's face it, that's just a smaller
lonely room filled with comic books.
(Leonard:)Thanks, Stuart.
(Leonard:)Let me ask you.
Do you think it's okay to have
an ex-boyfriend sleep on her couch?
(Howard:)-She's obviously way out of line.
-Thank you.
(Howard:)But if she dumps you,
she'll have a new boyfriend by tomorrow...
(Howard:)...and you'll have a new girlfriend
when you figure out how to build one.
(Howard:)So the only question is,
how long until you fold?